Guide to the Department of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011.
Johnson Graduate School of Management Department of Marketing and Communications records, 1997-2011
- Series II. Photographs
  - Photographs by date
    - Park Leadership Series: Jay Walker, 2000-04-13 (Box 10)
    - Family Picnic, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Abby Joseph Cohen, 2000-10-27 (Box 10)
    - Hatfield Lecture: Robert C. Wright, 2000-11-09 (Box 10)
    - Durland Lecture: Craig Barrett, Intel, 2000-04 (Box 11)
    - Mentorship 2000 Student, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Staff Recognition Luncheon, 2000-06-12 (Box 11)
    - Week on Wall Street 2000, 2000 (Box 13)
    - State of the School 2000, 2000 (Box 13)
    - JGSM Commencement Awards brunch, 2000-05 (Box 13)
    - PBS/CEO Exchange March 2000, 2000-03 (Box 13)
    - Technology symposium 2000, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Park Fellows 2000 Presentation, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Fried Fellows April 2000, 2000-04 (Box 13)
    - Fried Fellows Photo 2001, 2001 (Box 11)
    - EVC Symposium, 2001 (Box 10)
    - State of the School, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Hall of Honor 2001: Parker and Marin, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Corp, Daniel Park Spcator, 2001-04 (Box 10)
    - BGBA, 2001 (Box 10)
    - T.J. Rodgers,Tech Symposium and Park Lecture, 2001-04 (Box 10)
    - Twelve Month Option Picnic, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Welcome Reception, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Orientation, 2001-2002 (Box 10)
    - Community Service Crossroads, 2001 (Box 10)
    - International Students Welcome, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Welcome Picnic, 2001 (Box 10)
    - BGBA Speaker Series, 2001-03 (Box 10)
    - Dean's Address, 2001-09 (Box 10)
    - Community Service Sciencenter, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Jeff Parker '01, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Community Service State Theatre, 2001 (Box 10)
    - BRUF Partners, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Entrepreneurship Luncheon Panel, 2001 (Box 10)
    - John Pepper, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Ken Chennautt and Trustee Reception, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Food Fight, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Park Lecture: Ben Zander, 2001-11 (Box 10)
    - MBA Intensive Ice Cream Social Incoming Class 2002, 2002 (Box 10)
    - EPI Symposium, 2002-02-08 (Box 10)
    - Tech Symp, 2002-03-08 (Box 10)
    - State of the School 2002, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Suter, Stanley, 2002-03-14 (Box 10)
    - Homecoming, 2002 (Box 10)
    - International Week Capucira, 2002-11 (Box 10)
    - Hannibal Johnson BGBA Speaker, 2003-02 (Box 10)
    - State of the School (SOTS) '03, 2003 (Box 10)
    - Sim Goarchian Glass, 2003-02 (Box 10)
    - EVC Symposium, 2003 (Box 10)
    - Class '03 Graduation, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Phonathon 2004, 2004 (Box 19)
    - Class of 2005 gift committee, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Professor Seymour Smidt and Scott Stewart, MBA '83, PhD '85, in the classroom named in Smidt's honor. 2005, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Ramesh Akella, MBA (E) '03, and Carmen Akella, MBA (E) '05, for 2005 Philanthropy Report, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Reunion 2005: Half Century club and speaker David Binder, MBA '80, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Reunion 2005 lo-res, 2005 (Box 19)
  - Photographs by event
    - Career Fair, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Business Simulation Lab, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Technology People Soft Lab, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - BRV, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Sidvey Tavrel, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Citigroup/Office for Women and Minorities in Business (OWMB) In NY, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - PhD area and party, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Eron Pavel, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Charity Askin, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Bogle, John Park speaker, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - GM Project, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - BRV, Big Idea, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Sumo wrestling, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Hawton lecture, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Entrepreneur, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Reuteger Lecture, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Hottonlocker with the Neafseys, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Trustee Recognition, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - AJ. Cohen, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Apple Award, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Ken Blanchard, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Kopp, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Fried Fellows, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Big Idea Competition, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - BRU and BRJ, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Alan Siegel, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Biotech Symposium, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - European Symposium, Date Unknown (Box 10)
    - Just About Jobs, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Charity Auction, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Sandy Weill, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Stock Pitch, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Lin Draper - Durland Lecture, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Iron Chef, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Ray Anderson, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Park Project, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Sammy's, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Staff and Faculty Awards, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Twelve Month Option (TMO) ice cream social, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Grad week Canoe race, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Grad week Hike, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Grad week golf, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Grad week sailing, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Dean's Awards Lunch, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Analytical Thinking, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - CMC Alumni Park, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - BGBA Awards - Wilbur Parker, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - BGBA Symposium, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Sustainable Business Symposium, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Survey Data, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - James Benning, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Black Graduate Business Association (BGBA), Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Cayuga Press of Ithaca, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Crane Surveys, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Drive for five, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - E-Business Intensive, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Fast Forward Icon Photography, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Rich Marin '75, MBA '76, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - National Seminars Group, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - NY Times Meeting March 3, 2000, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Park Speaker 11/16/00 Jim Johnson, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Jeff Parker '65, MEng '66, MBA '70, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Prentice Hall - Permission Request, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Harvey Golub, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - JAG Members, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Johnson Family Trip, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Chuck Lee - GTE At JGSM, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Fried Fellows, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Minority Grad Business Assoc., Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Outward Bound and Executive Ventures, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Pimm, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - JBSM MBA Golf tournament 9/1998, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Malott Hall Resources, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Hall of Honor, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - International - general shots, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Historic Photos, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Durland Lecture Dennis Dammerman, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - EMBA Rare Books Session For Econ., Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - NY Times Photos, Date Unknown (Box 11)
    - Sage Cornerstone Celebration, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Steve Johansson, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Sage Hall, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Clint Sidle Release, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Weill Fellowship release, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Brochure release, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Robert H. Frank, The Winner-Take-All Society, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Admissions reprint, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Hyundu stories, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - BW top entry teachers, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Scientist as manager reprints, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - News envelopes, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Merten media, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Access Training, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Advocacy initiative, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Media Ideas, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Park Speakers, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Staff and Faculty Contacts '96, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Michael Hostetler, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Steve Sharratt, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Gene L. Ziegler, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Phonathon Photos, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    - Seneca Falls Trip Office for Women and Minorites in Business (OWMB), Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - USA Today (Charles Lee Article), Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Internship brochure, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Johnson School Activities, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Minority Reception, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Week in Silicon Valley, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - EMBA Library Visit, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Park Speaker Photos Orit Gadiesh, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Hillary Clinton and President Rawlings, Date Unknown (Box 13)
    - Capital Campaign Kickoff Dinner, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Class Challenge Giving Cup (S.C. Johnson cup), Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Combat Tournament, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Mock presentations, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - European Alumni symposium, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Durland Lecture Series (5 folders), Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Dean Tarr, Date Unknown (Box 16)
    - Merten, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Quality of student life Study Mark Sheridan, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Outdoor Leadership, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Sports, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Advisory Council, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Alumni Association, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Energy Conference, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Students at play - Community weekend, Jerry Hass's party, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Minority Graduate Bus. Assoc., Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Black & Hispanic Student Association, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Catalog: Faculty Bio, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Catalog: printer problems, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Catalog: Faculty info, Date Unknown (Box 17)
    - Womens' Forum '76, '78, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Commencement '87, '88, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - VIP dinners (including Sanford Weill) (7 folders), Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Fried Fellows, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Friends of the school - including Sam Johnson, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Marketing Group, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Minority Forums, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Public Investments Panel, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Railroad Conference, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Former Faculty (2 folders), Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Johnson Distinguished Lectures (5 folders), Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Guest Speakers: Randy Allen and Joseph Seale, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Alan Master, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - S.C. Johnson and Son Board of Directors, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Advertising Debate, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Arts Conference, Date Unknown (Box 18)
    - Hatfield Fellow Lectures, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Felix Rouse, MBA '03, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Timline Photos, Enterprise spring 2006: Johnson School Deans: O'Keary, Litchfield, Joe Bridy, MBA â04, pard, Merton, Davidson, Curtis Tarr, David A. Thomas, Swieringa. McGraw 1946. Malott 1964. Class of 1948. Post WWII Veterans. Advisory Council meeting fall 1994. Malott Hall, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Ken Gurrola, MBA '95, and Gerry Curciarello, MBA '75, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Admissions/career article - Salaries by type of Industry / Job Function - Class of 1990, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Johnson School mugs (1 slide), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Misc. Portraits - no dates or identifications except one 1992 slide, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Dean's Recognition Dinner (3 folders), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Library (2 folders), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Semester in Manufacturing (3 folders), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Task Force, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Commencement 1993, 89, 92 (7 folders), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Minority Forum, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Malott Times (2 folders), Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Lifelong learning, CASE Dit 1990, Date Unknown (Box 19)
    - Entrepreneurship chair endowment event, Date Unknown (Box 22)
    - Executive Development Program, Date Unknown (Box 22)
    - International Programs, Date Unknown (Box 22)
    - International Studies, Date Unknown (Box 22)
    - Assorted Conference, Date Unknown (Box 22)
- Series III. Ephemera
  - Class of 1948 Reunion T-Shirt (Box 5)
  - "Pipeline to the 21st Century: Changing the Face of Corporate America"-PhotoSynthesis Producations, October 16, 2003; V-6267 (Box 7)
  - "CEO Exchange"-PBS Video, 2000; V-6268 (Box 7)
  - Sage Hall Dedication photos - 2 CDs, Date Unknown; CD-5147-5148 (Box 7)
  - Sage Hall renderings CD, 1996-12-02; CD-5149 (Box 7)
  - Johnson School photo CDs, Date Unknown; CD-5150-5156
  - VHS videos (2): "Welcome to the Sage Hall Dedication", Date Unknown; V-11665-11666 (Box 7)
  - VHS video: Seymour Smidt classroom dedication, Oct. 15,2005, 2005-10-15; V-11664 (Box 7)
  - Brussels '94 scrapbooks, 1994-03-18-1994-03-20 (Box 28)
- Johnson Documents
  - Faculty, Staff, and Student Directory, 1987-1988, 1994-1997 (Box 13)
  - Faculty & Staff Directory, 1997-1999 (Box 13)
  - Student Directory, 1997-2001 (Box 13)
  - Johnson School Community Directory Faculty, Staff & Adminsistration, and Students, 2001-2008, 2013-2014 (Box 13)
  - Class of 2006, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Lead 2004 Johnson Means Business (JMB) 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 13)
  - Johnson Outdoor Experience (JOE), 2002 (Box 13)
  - Executive Education MBA, Date Unknown (Box 13)
  - Business ofâ¦, 2005 (Box 13)
  - JMB '01 '02 '03 '04, 2001-2004 (Box 13)
  - EMBA '01 - '02, 2001-2002 (Box 13)
  - Camp Start Up '02 '03 '05, Date Unknown (Box 13)
  - Executive Education & EMBA Programs '98-'00, 1998-2000 (Box 14)
  - Destination Johnson, 1999-2003 (Box 14)
  - Exec Ed Programs Slides 1993- 1997, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Giving Portraits, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Sage Hall, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Leadership week, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Parker Center, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Park '03 '04, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Assorted Alumni, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Lead 2002, 2003, 2004, Date Unknown (Box 15)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley 2002, 2002 (Box 15)
  - Sage Hall Book, Date Unknown (Box 15)
  - Fast Forward, 1998-05 (Box 15)
  - Untitled black binder, Date Unknown (Box 15)
  - Class of 1992, Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Week on Wall St '99 (1-2), 1999 (Box 16)
  - Silicon Valley 1999, 1999 (Box 16)
  - U-Photo Digital Jobs, 2003-2004 (Box 16)
  - Class 1994, Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Class 1991, Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Symposia & Visiting speakers, 2004-09-2004-11 (Box 16)
  - Portraits, Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Older slides before MSG (1-2), Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Interior/Exterior Sage Hall, Date Unknown (Box 16)